Preliminary Guide to the Kenneth W. Brooks Architectural Drawings 1963-circa 1999
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Preliminary Guide to the Kenneth W. Brooks Architectural Drawings
1963-circa 1999
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
MS 2022.01
Brooks, Kenneth W., 1917-1996
14.9 Linear feet of shelf space 5 Oversize folders
This collection consists of over 200 architectural drawings by Spokane architect Kenneth Brooks.
Architect Kenneth W. Brooks was born in Cedarvale, Kansas in 1917. He received his undergraduate degree in Architectural Engineering in 1941 and a master's degree in Architecture in 1948, both from the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign. He served in the Caribbean with the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers (1941-1943) and the U.S. Marine Corps (1944-1946).
In 1948 Brooks traveled to Europe on a University of Illinois Francis Plym Fellowship, spending most of his seven-month trip in Sweden working with Sven Markelius, a Swedish city planner and architect.
He moved to Spokane in 1948 and established his architectural practice there in 1951 (Kenneth Brooks, Architect; later Brooks, Hensley, Creager). He became an award-winning urban designer and city planner; one of his most ambitious and noteworthy projects was "A Place in the Sun," an urban design plan for downtown Spokane. He participated very actively in the planning process for Expo '74, the World's Fair held in Spokane in 1974. He designed several major commercial buildings, including the headquarters for Washington Water Power in Spokane, the Rogers-Orton Dining Hall at Washington State University, the Intermountain Gas Company Central Service Facility in Boise, and the art-music-drama complex at Columbia Basin Community College in Pasco, Washington.
Brooks was very active in his profession, frequently presenting papers to local, regional, and national groups on topics in architecture, urban design, transportation planning, and environmental policy.
Source: Kenneth W. Brooks Papers, 1936-1992 (Cage 685) Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Washington State University Libraries
This collection consists of over 200 architectural drawings by Spokane architect Kenneth Brooks. The bulk of the collection is plans for the Deaconess Hospital Addition in Spokane; also included are plans for Spokane Fire Department buildings, the Stevens County Courthouse remodel, the Community Congregational Church in Veradale, Washington, and the Mount Carmel Hospital addition and remodel in Colville, Washington.
This is an unprocessed collection. Any arrangement reflects either a pre-existing order from the records’ creator or preliminary sorting performed by staff.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Barbara Brooks donated this collection to the Washington State University Libraries in 2022 (MS 2022.01).
The repository expects to receive additions to this collection.
Kenneth W. Brooks Papers, 1936-1992 (Cage 685)
Kenneth W. Brooks Papers, 1959-2000 (Cage 775)
Kenneth W. Brooks Oral History, 1988 July 25 (CT 24)
Preliminary Guide to the Donald Howard Murray Papers, 1922-1983 (MS 2022.07)
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Brooks, Kenneth W., 1917-1996 -- Archives
Architects -- Northwest, Pacific -- Archives; Architects -- Washington (State) -- Spokane -- Archives; Architecture -- Washington (State)
Spokane; Architecture
- Folder 1
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Precast Concrete Panel Elevations:: North and South Elevations [AS-3] with Field Observations (Copy, Diazo, Acetate), 1981 (Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Precast Concrete Panel Elevations:: East and West Elevations [AS-3] with Field Observations (Copy, Diazo, Acetate), 1981 (Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Ambulance Drive Paving Layout [AS 137] (Original Drawing, Polyester), 1980 (Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: First Floor Plan Tower:: Revisions One [A-4] (Acetate Diazo), 1979 (Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Second Floor Plan Tower:: Interior Wall Surface Paint Schedule [A-5] (Diazo Acetate), 1980 (Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: Third Floor Plan Tower:: Obstetrics [A-6] (Acetate Diazo), 1979 (Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: Third Floor Plan Tower:: Obstetrics::: Interior Wall Surface Paint Schedule [A-6] (Acetate Diazo), 1979 (Folder 1, Item 7)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Fourth Floor Plan Tower:: Interior Wall Surface Paint Schedule [A-7] (acetate diazo), 1979 (Folder 1, Item 8)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Seventh Floor Plan Tower:: Interior Wall Surface Paint Schedule [A-10] (acetate diazo), 1979 (Folder 1, Item 9)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Eighth Floor Plan Tower:: Interior Wall Surface Paint Schedule [A-11] (acetate diazo), 1979 (Folder 1, Item 10)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Ninth Floor Plan Tower:: Interior Wall Surface Paint Schedule [A-12] (acetate diazo), 1979 (Folder 1, Item 11)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Tenth Floor Plan Tower:: Interior Wall Surface Paint Schedule [A-12] (acetate diazo), 1979 (Folder 1, Item 12)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Eleventh Floor Plan Tower:: Ninth, Tenth, Eleventh Floor Plans MSU (Medical Surveillance Unit) [A-12], 1979 (Folder 1, Item 13)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Eleventh Floor Plan Tower:: Ninth, Tenth, Eleventh Floor Plans MSU (Medical Surveillance Unit) [A-12] with notes, 1979 (Folder 1, Item 14)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Roof Plan Tower Helistop with Notes:: Roof Plan, Mechanical Penthouse Plan, Penthouse Roof Plans, Helistop Edge, Walk Edge, Floor Drain, Wall Section, Helistop Markings [A-13], 1979 (Folder 1, Item 15)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Exterior Elevations:: Surgery North and South Elevations, Nursing North and South Elevations, Corner Detail, Partial North and South Elevations, A and B Elevations [A-14], 1979 (Folder 1, Item 16)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Construction Canopy: Exterior Elevations:: Surgery North and South Elevations, Nursing North and South Elevations, Corner Detail, Partial North and South Elevations, A and B Elevations [A-14] with Notes, 1979 (Folder 1, Item 17)
  - Deaconess Hospital Canopy Construction: Exterior Elevations:: Surgery East and West Elevations, Nursing East and West Elevations, Partial West Elevation, L and J and K Elevations [A-15], 1979 (Folder 1, Item 18)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: Building Sections Tower [A-17], 1979 (Folder 1, Item 19)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: Typical Wall Sections Tower [A-20] with Notes, 1979 (Folder 1, Item 20)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: Details (structural) [A-21A], 1979 (Folder 1, Item 21)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: Miscellaneous Reflected Ceiling Plans:: Partial Third Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan, Fourth Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan, Reflected Soffit Plans Canopy, Partial Sixth Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan [A-27A], 1979 (Folder 1, Item 22)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Fourth Floor Plan Surgery [A-31], 1979 (Folder 1, Item 23)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Fourth Floor Plan Surgery:: Interior Wall Surface Paint Schedule [A-31], 1980 (Folder 1, Item 24)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Fourth Floor Surgery:: Record Drawing [A-31], 1980 (Folder 1, Item 25)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Interior Elevations Surgery:: Record Drawing [A-44], 1980 (Folder 1, Item 26)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Interior Elevations Surgery:: Record Drawing [A-45], 1980 (Folder 1, Item 27)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Interior Elevations Surgery:: Record Drawing [A-46], 1980 (Folder 1, Item 28)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Special Millwork and Casework:: Revised to show Not In Contract work [A-50], 1981 (Folder 1, Item 29)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: Nursing Tower Foundation Plan:: Footing and Foundation Plan, Concrete Column Schedule, Footings Schedule, Structural Notes [S-1], 1980 (Folder 1, Item 30)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: Nursing Tower First Floor Plan [S-2] with revisions, 1979 (Folder 1, Item 31)
  - Deaconess Hospital Construction Canopy: Nursing Tower Second and Partial Third Floor Plan [S-3], 1979 (Folder 1, Item 32)
- Folder 2
  - Deaconess Hospital-Phase Two Construction: Cover Illustration (pencil and pen on polyester), 0 (Folder 2, Item 33)
  - Deaconess Hospital Remodel: Central Services Floor Plan (Basement of Phase Two) [A-1], 1974 (Folder 2, Item 34)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Site Plan and Site Details:: Index of drawings and legal description of site [A-1] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 35)
  - Deaconess Hospital Remodel: Parking Lot 'D' Site Plan [A-2], 0 (Folder 2, Item 36)
  - Deaconess Hospital Remodel: Central Services Reflected Ceiling Plan (Basement Floor) [A-3], 1974 (Folder 2, Item 37)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Basement Plan [A-2] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 38)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: First Floor Plan [A-3] Phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 39)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase II Proposed Revision of Fourth Floor Plan - Radiology Department [A-6R], 1972 (Folder 2, Item 40)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Cardiac Care Unit; Intensive Care Unit [A 4] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 41)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase II Third Floor Plan:: Advanced Care Unit [A 5], 1972 (Folder 2, Item 42)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase II Fourth Floor Plan:: Radiology, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 43)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase II Fourth Floor Plan:: Supplementary Wall Backing -Notes [A-6], 1973 (Folder 2, Item 44)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Fifth Floor and Roof Plan [A 7], 1972 (Folder 2, Item 45)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase II Sixth Floor Plan, Seventh Floor Plan, Roof Plan [A 8], 1972 (Folder 2, Item 46)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: North Elevation and Exit Window Details [A-9] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 47)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: East and South Exterior Elevations and Sky Light Details [A-10] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 48)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: West Exterior Elevations and Skylight Details [A-11] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 49)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Elevations - Sections C-C; D-D; E-E, and Details [A-12] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 50)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Building Section FF [A-13] phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 51)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Partial Building Sections GG [A 15] Phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 52)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Partial Building Sections GG [A 15] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 53)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Wall Sections; Exterior Details [A 16] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 54)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Exterior Details [A 17] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 55)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Stair Number One, Plans; Sections and Details [A-18] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 56)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase II Door and Relite Details [A 19], 1972 (Folder 2, Item 57)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Miscellaneous Details [A-20] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 58)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: First Floor Interior Elevations [A-21] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 59)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: First Floor Interior Elevations [A-22] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 60)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: First Floor Interior Elevations [A-23] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 61)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Second Floor Interior Elevations [A-24] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 62)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Second Floor Interior Elevations [A-24] Phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 63)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Second Floor Interior Elevations [A-26] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 64)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Second Floor Interior Elevations [A-27] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 65)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Second Floor Interior Elevations [A-28] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 66)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Third Floor Interior Elevation [A-29] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 67)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Third Floor Interior Elevation [A-30] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 68)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Third Floor Interior Elevations [A-31] Phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 69)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Fourth Floor Interior Elevations [A-32] Phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 70)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Fourth Floor Interior Elevations [A-33] Phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 71)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Fourth Floor Interior Elevations [A-34] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 72)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Future Construction Phase II:: Fourth Floor Interior Elevation [A-34A], 0 (Folder 2, Item 73)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Future Construction, Phase II:: Fourth Floor Interior Elevation [A-35B], 0 (Folder 2, Item 74)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Interior Details [A-35] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 75)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Basement Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan [A 36] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 76)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: First Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan [A 37] Phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 77)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: First Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan [A 37] Phase II First Revision, 0 (Folder 2, Item 78)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Second Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan [A 38] Phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 79)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Second Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan [A 38] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 80)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Third Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan [A 39] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 81)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Third Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan [A 39] Phase II, 0 (Folder 2, Item 82)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Fourth, Fifth, and Sixth Floor Reflected Ceiling Plans [A 40] Phase II (Folder 2, Item 83)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Fourth, Fifth, and Sixth Floor Reflected Ceiling Plans [A 40] Phase II Third Revisions (Folder 2, Item 84)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Bridge- Composite Section Details [C-1] Phase II, 1972 (Folder 2, Item 85)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Nurses' Stations and Monitors (Casework Drawings), 1973 (Folder 2, Item 86)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Nurses' Stations and Monitors (Casework Drawings) [AS-49], 1973 (Folder 2, Item 87)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Landscape Planting Plan [AS-39], 1973 (Folder 2, Item 88)
- Folder 3
  - Deaconess Master Plan Scheme: B Level: +1 (1968'), 0 (Folder 3, Item 89)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Scheme: B Level: +3 (1989'), 0 (Folder 3, Item 90)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Level: +3 1/2 (1994'), 0 (Folder 3, Item 91)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Level: +4 (2000') (Folder 3, Item 92)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Level: +5 (2010') (Folder 3, Item 93)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Level: +6 (2024') (Folder 3, Item 94)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Section A-A, Section B-B, Section C-C, 0 (Folder 3, Item 95)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Section D-D, Section E-E, Section F-f, 0 (Folder 3, Item 96)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Scheme: B Level: +4 (2000') (Folder 3, Item 97)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Level: -2 (1934'), 0 (Folder 3, Item 98)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Level -1 (1953'), 0 (Folder 3, Item 99)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Level +1 (1968'), 0 (Folder 3, Item 100)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Level: +2 1/4 (1981'), 0 (Folder 3, Item 101)
  - Deaconess Hospital Master Plan Space Program and Placement, 0 (Folder 3, Item 102)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Post Phase Three Nursing Service Distribution, 0 (Folder 3, Item 103)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Post Phase Three Nursing Service Distribution FINAL, 1980 (Folder 3, Item 104)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Current Nursing Service Distribution, 1984 (Folder 3, Item 105)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Current Nursing Service Distribution Overlay, 0 (Folder 3, Item 106)
  - Deaconess Hospital: Current Nursing Service Distribution Overlay with Ground, 0 (Folder 3, Item 107)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Basement and Foundation Plan, Wall Sections, Footing Schedule [S-1] (Copy and Whiteprint), 1972 (Folder 3, Item 108)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: First Floor Framing Plan [S-2 Phase Two] (Copy and Whiteprint), 1972 (Folder 3, Item 109)
  - Proposed Plan: Cystoscopy/Film Assembly/Sub sterile (Original Drawing, Vellum), 1978 (Folder 3, Item 110)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Precast Concrete Panel Elevations:: North and South Elevations [AS-3], 1979 (Folder 3, Item 111)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Construction: Precast Concrete Panel Elevations:: East and West Elevations [AS-3], 1979 (Folder 3, Item 112)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: View Looking East From Lincoln Street, 1971 (Folder 3, Item 113)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Site Plan, Index of Drawings, General Notes, Legal Description of Site [A-1], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 114)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Chiller Plant Plans Site Retaining Wall Elevations [A-2], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 115)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Chiller Plant Elevations and Building Sections [A-3], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 116)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Wall Sections and Details [A-4], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 117)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Service Link Plan Sections and Elevations [A-5], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 118)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Service Link Details and Autopsy Plan and Elevations [A-6], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 119)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Storage Building Plans [A-7], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 120)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Storage Building Plans [A-8], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 121)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Service and Pipe Tunnels Plans; Second, Ground, Terrace Level Plans and Notes [A-9], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 122)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Service and Pipe Tunnel Sections and Details [A-10], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 123)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase I Clarification and Supplemental Details At Terrace and Pipe Tunnels [AS-11], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 124)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Soil Investigation (Phase One), 1971 (Folder 3, Item 125)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Chiller Plant Plans and Sections [S-1], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 126)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase I Chiller Plant, Roof Plan, Wall Sections [S-2], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 127)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase Once Service Link, Plans and Sections:: Plan showing existing construction to remain and to remove [S-3], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 128)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Storage Building, Floor and Foundation Plan, Ground Floor Plan [S-4], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 129)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Storage Building Roof Framing Plan [S-5], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 130)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Sections, Detains and Typical Notes [S-6], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 131)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Service and Pipe Tunnels Plan and Section [S-7], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 132)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Phase One Service and Pipe Tunnels Plans and Sections [S-8], 1971 (Folder 3, Item 133)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Unistrut Framing: Radiology Department Revisions Change Proposal G-16 [SS-17], 1972 (Folder 3, Item 134)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Unistrut Framing Details: Radiology Department Revisions Change Proposal G-16 [SS-18], 1972 (Folder 3, Item 135)
- Folder 4
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three Studies for Nursing Tower Relocation (5 pages), 1978 (Folder 4, Item 136)
  - Deaconess Master Plan Scheme: B Level: +1 (1968'); Level: +3 (1989'); Level: +4 (2000') (Folder 4, Item 137)
  - Overlay Sketch of Deaconess Hospital: Floor with existing Surgery and Radiology, 0 (Folder 4, Item 138)
  - Deaconess Hospital East-West Section Site Three on Vellum, 0 (Folder 4, Item 139)
  - Deaconess Hospital East-West Section Site, Vellum, 0 (Folder 4, Item 140)
  - Deaconess Hospital Sections D-D, E-E, F-F on Vellum, 0 (Folder 4, Item 141)
  - Undated perspective sketch of Deaconess Hospital on Vellum, 0 (Folder 4, Item 142)
  - Deaconess Hospital South-North Sections A-A, B-B, C-C on Vellum, 0 (Folder 4, Item 143)
  - Deaconess Phase Four Ancillary Structure Space Diagram (10 pages) pg1: Section A; pg2: Level-3 Utilities and Shops (Shell); pg3: Level -2 Shops and Storage (Shell); pg4: Level -1 Storage (Shell); pg5: Level +1 Dining and Kitchen (Shell); pg6: Level +3 Obs, 1980 (Folder 4, Item 144)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three: Seventh, Eighth, Ninth, Tenth, and Eleventh Floor Plans [9], 1978 (Folder 4, Item 145)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three: South Elevation [12], 1978 (Folder 4, Item 146)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three: Perspective [1], 1978 (Folder 4, Item 147)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three: Eighth, Ninth, Tenth, Eleventh Floor Plans:: Typical M/S Floor [10], 1978 (Folder 4, Item 148)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three: North Elevation [13], 1978 (Folder 4, Item 149)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three: First Floor Plan [4], 1978 (Folder 4, Item 150)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three: East-West Section Copy, 0 (Folder 4, Item 151)
  - Deaconess Hospital Addition: Site Plan, 0 (Folder 4, Item 152)
  - Deaconess Hospital Phase Three: Typical Patient Room:: One Point Perspective Drawing [11], 1978 (Folder 4, Item 153)
  - N. 508 Wall Street, Spokane, WA: Alarm Center (Remodel) Floor Plan, Reflected Ceiling Plan, Interior Elevations [A-1] (Folder 4, Item 154)
  - 121 South Wall Street, 99204 Demolition Plans and Details [M-1] (Folder 4, Item 155)
  - 121 South Wall Street, 99204 HVAC and Piping Plans [M-2] (Folder 4, Item 156)
  - Spokane Fire Department Alarm Center: Symbols, Notes and Fixture Schedule with revisions [E-1], 1991 (Folder 4, Item 157)
  - Spokane Fire Department Alarm Center: Lighting, Power and System Plans with revisions [E-2], 1991 (Folder 4, Item 158)
  - Spokane Fire Department Alarm Center: Demolition Plans and Details [M-1], 1991 (Folder 4, Item 159)
  - Spokane Fire Department Alarm Center: HVAC and Piping Plans [M-2], 1991 (Folder 4, Item 160)
  - Spokane Fire Department Alarm Center: Symbols, Notes and Fixture Schedule [E-1], 1991 (Folder 4, Item 161)
  - Spokane Fire Department Alarm Center: Lighting, Power and System Plans [E-2], 1991 (Folder 4, Item 162)
  - Fire Station Number One (Remodel) Cover Sheet [A-1], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 163)
  - Fire Station Number One (Remodel) West 44 Riverside Spokane, Washington: First Floor Plan/Partial Basement Plan with notes and planting notes [A-2], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 164)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Second Floor Plan, Mezzanine Plan, Mezzanine Framing [A-3], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 165)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Enlarged Plans; Stair Section/Details; Wall Sections [A-4], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 166)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Details [A-5], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 167)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Interior Elevations [A-6], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 168)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Interior Elevations/Partial Exterior Elevations [A-7], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 169)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Reflected Ceiling Plans [A-8], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 170)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) First Floor/Basement Piping Plan [M-2], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 171)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) First Floor/ Basement HVAC [M-3], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 172)